Welcome to the unit Animals in the Wild A.
How much do you know about wild animals?
Write the correct names under the pictures.
Then listen to the introductions to learn more about these animals. 1.
I'm big, brown and brave.
I have large wings.
I have good eyes and can see my food from way up high. 2.
I live in the ocean.
My skin is smooth and I have a pointed mouth.
I'm usually grey in colour.
I really like to play.
I can jump high out of the water. 3.
I live in Africa in a big group.
I eat grass and small plants.
I have a long neck and I look like a horse.
I am black and white. 4.
I have a pointed face and look like a wolf.
My legs are thin.
I'm usually red in colour and I often sleep in a hole in the ground. 5.
I like to live in groups.
I can hear and smell things far away.
I can run for hours without stopping. 6.
I live in the ocean. I'm large.
I have no bones.
I eat a lot and I have about 3,000 teeth.
My sense of smell is much better than humans.